Guide to the Frederick W. Hilles Manuscript Collection and Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Frederick W. Hilles Manuscript Collection, 1645–1969; Series I; 17.94; 41 boxes + 1 broadside.
  - Carlyle Manuscripts, 1645–1911
    - Correspondence, 1772–1911
      - Outgoing, 1818–1911
        - Carlyle, Thomas, 1865 October 30 (Box 22, Folder 724)
          Autograph letter, signed, to Alexander T. Taetgen, from Chelsea, 1 page.
        - Carlyle, Thomas, 1830 July 24 (Box 22, Folder 725)
          Autograph letter, signed, to William Tait, from Craigenputtock, 3 pages.
        - Carlyle, Thomas, 1860 November 28 (Box 22, Folder 726)
          Autograph letter, signed, to Mr. Taylor, from Chelsea, 2 pages.
        - Carlyle, Thomas, 1823–1825 (Box 22, Folder 727)
          Two autograph letters, signed, to John Taylor.
        - Carlyle, Thomas, 1872 May 26 (Box 22, Folder 728)
          Autograph letter, signed, to Clara H. Thomson, from Chelsea, 4 pages.
        - Carlyle, Thomas, 1865 July 8 (Box 22, Folder 729)
          Autograph letter written in the third person, signed, to Nicholas Trübner, from the Gill, Annan, 1 page.
        - Carlyle, Thomas, 1866 December 13 (Box 22, Folder 730)
          Autograph letter, signed, to Madame Venturi, from Chelsea, 2 pages.
        - Carlyle, Thomas, 1842-1860; 1911 February 27 (Box 22, Folder 731)
          Five typescripts of letters to William Warren Vernon. Accompanied by an autograph letter, signed, from Vernon to Mr. Sterling, 1911 February 27. Also includes an autograph letter, signed, from Carlyle to "Mrs. Welsh, 1842 November 19.
        - Carlyle, Thomas, 1865 April 21 (Box 23, Folder 732)
          Autograph letter, signed, to Mr. Watkins, from Chelsea, 4 pages. Includes a photograph of Carlyle pasted on page 1 and a manuscript note, signed "GF," on a separate slip pasted to the left edge.
        - Carlyle, Thomas, undated (Box 23, Folder 733)
          Autograph letter, signed, to Mrs. Wedgwood, from Chelsea, 2 pages.
        - Carlyle, Thomas, 1855 November 15 (Box 23, Folder 734)
          Autograph letter, signed, to Messrs. Williams & Norgate, from Chelsea, 1 page. Includes a portion of the catalogue of M. L. St. Goar tipped on.
        - Carlyle, Thomas, 1877 December 29 (Box 23, Folder 735)
          Letter written in the third person in the hand of an amanuensis to Mrs. Thomas Wright, from Chelsea, 1 page.
      - Incoming, 1772–1902
        - Baring, William Bingham, 2nd Baron Ashburton, 1857 March 20?; 1857 March 10 (Box 23, Folder 736)
          Autograph letter, signed, to Thomas Carlyle, from London, 1 page. Hinged to an autograph letter, signed, from Carlyle to Sir Lewis Pelly, from Chelsea, 1 page, with a note, signed with initials, by Pelly.
        - Bunsen, Baron Christian, 1843 July 4 (Box 23, Folder 737)
          Autograph letter, signed, to Thomas Carlyle, 2 pages.
        - Cavaignac, Godefroi, 1837 July 24 (Box 23, Folder 738)
          Autograph letter, signed, to Thomas Carlyle, from London, 5 pages.
        - Conway, Henry Seymour, 1788 January 20 (Box 23, Folder 739)
          Autograph letter, possibly signed by Conway, to an unidentified recipient, 1 page.
        - Conway, Henry Seymour, 1772 September 17 (Box 23, Folder 740)
          Autograph letter, signed, to William? Eden, from Berlin, 4 pages. Includes pencil annotations, possibly in the hand of Thomas Carlyle.
        - Doyle, Henry, undated (Box 23, Folder 741)
          Sketch, in ink, of Thomas Carlyle, 1 leaf.
        - Froude, James Anthony, 1868 January 5 (Box 23, Folder 742)
          Autograph letter, signed, to Thomas Carlyle, from London, 2 pages.
        - Holden?, Mary Carlyle, 1902 October 17 (Box 23, Folder 743)
          Autograph letter, signed, to Dewitt Miller, from Hamilton, Ontario, 3 pages.
        - Hunt, James Henry Leigh, undated (Box 23, Folder 744)
        - Jones, J. E., 1865 February 21 (Box 23, Folder 745)
          Autograph letter, signed, to Thomas Carlyle, from London, 2 pages. Contains a list of books charged out from the London Library by Carlyle, with Carlyle's notations on the locations of the books, signed and dated.
        - Lecky, William Edward Hartpole, undated (Box 23, Folder 746)
          Autograph letter, signed, to Thomas Carlyle, from London, 1 page.
        - M. W., 1850 (Box 23, Folder 747)
          Autograph manuscript review of Carlyle's New Treatise, Latter-Day Pamphlets, No. I, 16 pages.
        - Macready, W. C., 1845 July 21 (Box 23, Folder 748)
          Autograph letter, signed, to Thomas Carlyle, 3 pages, Includes a manuscript note, signed "T. C.," on page 4.
        - Müller, Max, 1874 May 30 (Box 23, Folder 749)
          Autograph letter, signed, to Thomas Carlyle, from Oxford, 2 pages.
        - Novice, G. W., 1869 October 26 (Box 23, Folder 750)
          Autograph letter, signed, to Thomas Carlyle, from Edinburgh, 2 pages. Includes an autograph note by Carlyle on page 4.
        - Parsons, T. (or I.) R., 1866 October 23 (Box 23, Folder 751)
          Autograph letter, signed, to Mr. Tait, from London, 2 pages. Includes an autograph letter, signed, from Carlyle to Thomas Woolner on page 2.
        - Proctor, Bryan Waller, 1866 November 5 (Box 23, Folder 752)
        - Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1833 October 29 (Box 23, Folder 753)
          Autograph letter, signed, to John Stirling, from London, 2 pages.
        - Sterling, John, 1835–1842 (Box 23, Folder 754)
          Twelve autograph letters, signed, to Thomas Carlyle. Accompanied by two autograph letters, signed, from Sterling to John Aitken Carlyle and an autograph letter, signed, from Sterling to Jane Welsh Carlyle, enclosing an autograph letter, signed, to Thomas Carlyle.
        - Tait, Robert, 1874? July 21; 1874 July 21 (Box 23, Folder 755)
          Autograph letter, signed, to Thomas Carlyle, from London, 4 pages.
        - Tennyson, Alfred, 1st Baron Tennyson, 1842 December 9 (Box 23, Folder 756)
          Autograph letter, signed, to Thomas Carlyle, 4 pages.
    - Photographs, 1857
      - Photograph of Thomas Carlyle, 1857 December 29 (Box 23, Folder 757)
        Inscribed "yours truly."
      - Photographs, engravings, etc., of Thomas Carlyle., undated (Box 33 (Oversize), Folder 916)
        20 items
  - Johnson Manuscripts, 1773–1874
    - Andrews, E. A., circa 1821; 1816–1826 (Box 24, Folder 758)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley) Johnson, from Bath, 4 pages.
    - Andrews, Lady Elizabeth, 1799-1801? (Box 24, Folder 759)
      Two autograph letters, signed with initials, to Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley) Johnson. Includes an autograph letter, signed, from Elizabeth Anne Hunt to A. M. T. Johnson.
    - Andrews, Joseph, 1811 January 2 (Box 24, Folder 760)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley) Johnson, from Shaw Place, 1 page.
    - Brown, David, 1799 May 6 (Box 24, Folder 761)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley) Johnson, 2 pages.
    - Brown, David, 1799 October 13 (Box 24, Folder 762)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Richard Johnson, 1 page.
    - Brown, David, 1799 May (Box 24, Folder 763)
      Two autograph letters, signed, to John Johnson.
    - Cheesewright, Mr., 1841 December (Box 24, Folder 764)
      Three autograph letters, written in the third person, to Miss Johnson, from Harbertonford.
    - Tolley, William and Anna Marie, 1800 January 14 (Box 24, Folder 765)
      Manuscript copy of a document giving John Johnson and Richard Johnson power of attorney over the estates of William Tolley and Anna Maria Tolley, Calcutta, 12 pages.
    - Deane, Elizabeth (Johnson), 1815 June 1 (Box 24, Folder 766)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley) Johnson, from Torrington, 4 pages.
    - East India House, Accountants Office, 1804 July 21 (Box 24, Folder 767)
      Printed bill, completed in manuscript, sent to W. Johnston for payment of £2.4 by Hyde, Marter & Ball, 2 pages.
    - Furse, Peter Wellington ?, 1826-03-30-1826-03-30 (Box 24, Folder 768)
      Autograph letter to Joshua Reynolds Johnson, from Torrington, 3 pages. Includes an autograph letter, signed, from Charles William Johnson to Joshua Reynolds Johnson on page 4.
    - Garth, Ira ?, 1799 or later-1822; undated (Box 24, Folder 769-770)
      Sixty-four manuscript letters to "Mrs. Johnson."
    - Horsburgh, James ?, circa 1855; 1850–1860 (Box 24, Folder 771)
      Manuscript extract from Horsburgh's Directory, volume 1, page 47 ?, "Description of the Cape of Good Hope," 7 pages.
    - Hunt, Charles, 1813 May 29; undated (Box 24, Folder 772)
      Two autograph letters, signed, to an unidentified recipient, possibly Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley) Johnson.
    - Hunt, Elizabeth Anne, 1796–1822 (Box 24, Folder 773-774)
      Eighty autograph letters, signed, to Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley) Johnson. A complete list is filed with the letters.
    - Hunt, Elizabeth Anne, 1796–1822 (Box 25, Folder 775)
    - Hunt, Elizabeth Anne Andrews, 1786–1794 (Box 25, Folder 776)
      Fourteen manuscript letters to Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley) Johnson.
    - Johnson, Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley), 1802 March 22 (Box 25, Folder 777)
      Autograph letter, signed, to John Furse, 2 pages.
    - Johnson, Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley), 1803 December 31 (Box 25, Folder 778)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Mary (Johnson) Furse, from Polygon, Southampton, 4 pages.
    - Johnson, Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley), undated (Box 25, Folder 779)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Elizabeth and Frances Johnson, 4 pages.
    - Johnson, Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley), 1809 April 20; undated (Box 25, Folder 780)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Elizabeth and Frances Johnson, 1 page. Includes an undated autograph letter, signed, from Joshua Reynolds Johnson to Elizabeth and Frances Johnson on page 2.
    - Johnson, Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley), 1809 April 22 (Box 25, Folder 781)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Elizabeth Johnson, 3 pages.
    - Johnson, Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley), undated (Box 25, Folder 782)
      Autograph letter, signed, to "Brother," possibly Richard Johnson, 1 page.
    - Johnson, Anna Maria Tolley, 1804–1812 (Box 25, Folder 783)
      Letterbook containing copies of letters to Mr. Yonge, Mrs. Middleton, Messrs. Palmer, Mr. Coore, and Mr. Furse. Also includes a letter from Mr. Coore to Mrs. Johnson.
    - Johnson, Anna Maria Theresa, 1798 October?; 1798 October (Box 25, Folder 784)
      Letter to Lady Andrews, 3 pages.
    - Johnson, Charles William, undated (Box 25, Folder 785)
      Fragment of an autograph letter to an unidentified recipient, from Torrington, 1 page.
    - Johnson, Charles William, undated (Box 25, Folder 786)
      Fragment of an autograph letter, signed, to an unidentified recipient, 4 pages.
    - Johnson, Charles William, undated (Box 25, Folder 787)
      Fragment of an autograph letter to an unidentified recipient, 4 pages.
    - Johnson, Charles William, 1832–1836 (Box 26, Folder 788)
      Four autograph letters, signed, to his cousin.
    - Johnson, Charles William, 1844 July 19 (Box 26, Folder 789)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Sophia, 4 pages.
    - Johnson, Charles William, 1844–1852 (Box 26, Folder 790)
      Six autograph letters, signed, and two fragments of autograph letters to his cousin Theresa.
    - Johnson, Charles William, 1842–1845 (Box 26, Folder 791)
      Four autograph letters, signed, to Elizabeth M. Johnson, from Torrington.
    - Johnson, Charles William, 1800–1823; undated (Box 26, Folder 792)
      Fifteen autograph letters, signed, and one autograph letter to Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley) Johnson.
    - Johnson, Charles William, 1816–1840; undated (Box 26, Folder 793-798)
      One hundred fourteen autograph letters, signed, to Joshua Reynolds Johnson. A list of the letters is filed in the first folder.
    - Johnson, Charles William, 1835–1849; undated (Box 26, Folder 799)
      Nine autograph letters, signed, to Theresa Johnson.
    - Johnson, D., undated (Box 26, Folder 800)
      Fragment of an autograph letter to his cousin, 4 pages.
    - Johnson, D., 1802 March 16 (Box 26, Folder 801)
      Three autograph letters, signed, to his cousin.
    - Johnson, D., 1801 June 13 (Box 26, Folder 802)
      Three autograph letters, signed, to Mrs. Johnson.
    - Johnson, D., 1801 (Box 26, Folder 803)
      Two autograph letters, signed, to Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley) Johnson.
    - Johnson, Elizabeth, 1778 June 8 (Box 26, Folder 804)
      Autograph letter, signed, to William Johnson, from Halidon, 2 pages.
    - Johnson, Elizabeth, 1792 August 18 (Box 26, Folder 805)
      Autograph letter, signed, to William Johnson, from Torrington, 3 pages.
    - Johnson, Elizabeth M., 1809 April 19 (Box 26, Folder 806)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley) Johnson, from Sunning Hill, Berkshire, 2 pages.
    - Johnson, Elizabeth M., 1823 May 25 (Box 26, Folder 807)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley) Johnson, from Torrington, 3 pages. Includes an autograph letter, signed, from Charles William Johnson to Joshua Reynolds Johnson on page 3.
    - Johnson, Elizabeth M., 1840 January 30 (Box 26, Folder 808)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Joshua Reynolds Johnson, 4 pages.
    - Johnson, Elizabeth M., 1797 March-June; 1797 (Box 26, Folder 809)
      Manuscript journal titled "No. 4. (Copy) Journal three months. March 15th- June 6th 1797," 42 leaves, bound in marbled paper wrappers.
    - Johnson, Elizabeth M., 1797 August-September; 1797 (Box 26, Folder 810)
      Autograph manuscript journal titled "Betsy Johnson's Journal Second year commencing 31st August 1797," 11 leaves, in marbled paper wrappers.
    - Johnson, Elizabeth M., 1797 November (Box 26, Folder 811)
      Autograph manuscript journal, 9 leaves.
    - Johnson, Elizabeth M., 1798? February; 1798 February (Box 26, Folder 812)
      Autograph manuscript journal, 10 leaves.
    - Johnson, Elizabeth M., 1798 May-June; 1798 (Box 27, Folder 813)
      Autograph manuscript journal used in Calcutta, 20 leaves, in marbled paper wrappers.
    - Johnson, Elizabeth M., 1798 June-July; 1798 (Box 27, Folder 814)
      Autograph manuscript journal used in Calcutta, 19 leaves, in marbled wrappers.
    - Johnson, Elizabeth M., 1798 July-August; 1798 (Box 27, Folder 815)
      Autograph manuscript journal used in Calcutta, 21 leaves, in marbled paper wrappers.
    - Johnson, Elizabeth M., 1798 August-September; 1798 (Box 27, Folder 816)
    - Johnson, Elizabeth M., 1798 September-November; 1798 (Box 27, Folder 817)
      Autograph manuscript journal used in Calcutta, 19 leaves, in marbled paper wrappers.
    - Johnson, Elizabeth M., 1813 October 17 (Box 27, Folder 818)
      Autograph letter, signed, to "uncle," Mr. Johnson, from Wood Green, 1 page.
    - Johnson, Elizabeth M., 1837 April 15 (Box 27, Folder 819)
      Fragment of an autograph letter, signed with initials, to Joshua Johnson, 1 page.
    - Johnson, Frances, undated (Box 27, Folder 820)
    - Johnson, Frances Sophia, 1834 January 25 (Box 27, Folder 821)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Joshua Reynolds Johnson, 3 pages. Includes an autograph letter, signed, from Charles William Johnson to Joshua Reynolds Johnson on page 4.
    - Johnson, H., 1802–1804 (Box 27, Folder 822)
      Seven autograph letters, signed, to Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley) Johnson.
    - Johnson, Jane?, 1801 December 11 (Box 27, Folder 823)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley) Johnson, from Walthamstow, 4 pages.
    - Johnson, John, 1800–1804 (Box 27, Folder 824)
      Eleven autograph letters, signed, to Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley) Johnson.
    - Johnson, Joshua Reynolds, undated (Box 27, Folder 825)
      Sketch, in pencil, of "Binstead Church. Done by Joshua Reynolds Johnson at 8 years old."
    - Johnson, Joshua Reynolds, undated (Box 27, Folder 826)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley) Johnson, from Southampton, 1 page.
    - Johnson, Joshua Reynolds?, ? February 19 (Box 27, Folder 827)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley) Johnson, from Oxford, 1 page.
    - Johnson, Joshua Reynolds, undated (Box 27, Folder 828)
      Autograph letter, signed, to his sisters, from Battery, 3 pages.
    - Johnson, Joshua Reynolds, 1838 March 6 (Box 27, Folder 829)
      Fragment of an autograph letter, signed, to Elizabeth Johnson, 2 pages.
    - Johnson, Joshua Reynolds, undated (Box 27, Folder 830)
      Three autograph letters, signed, to Frances Johnson.
    - Johnson, Samuel, 1810–1811 (Box 27, Folder 831)
      Twelve autograph letters, signed, to Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley) Johnson.
    - Johnson, Samuel, ? February 20 (Box 27, Folder 832)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Richard Johnson, 3 pages.
    - Johnson, Samuel, 1777 April 16 (Box 27, Folder 833)
    - Johnson, Samuel, circa 1779; 1779 (Box 27, Folder 834)
      Autograph letter, written in the third person, to John Nichols, 1 page.
    - Johnson, Samuel, 1780 August 4 (Box 27, Folder 835)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Hester Lynch Thrale Piozzi, 3 pages.
    - Johnson, Samuel, 1784 September (Box 27, Folder 836)
      Copy of a letter by Johnson written in an unidentified hand to Lord Chancellor Thurlow, 2 pages. Also includes correspondence between Chapman, Hunt, Powell, and Hilles about the handwriting of the copy.
    - Johnson, Samuel, 1800 June 30 (Box 27, Folder 837)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Anne Maria Theresa Johnson, 6 pages.
    - Johnson, Theresa J., 1835 November 3 (Box 27, Folder 838)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Joshua Reynolds Johnson, 9 pages.
    - Johnson, Theresa J., 1836 April 8 (Box 27, Folder 839)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Joshua Reynolds Johnson, from Torrington, 2 pages. Includes a manuscript letter by an unidentified author to "Cousin Theresa" on page 3.
    - Johnson, Theresa J., 1829 June 18 (Box 27, Folder 840)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Mary Theresa Johnson, from Torrington, 2 pages.
    - Johnson, William, 1774 December 21 (Box 27, Folder 841)
      Manuscript copy in an unidentified hand of a letter to his mother, Elizabeth Johnson, from Calcutta, 7 pages.
    - Johnson, William, 1779 February 14 (Box 27, Folder 842)
      Autograph letter, signed, to his mother, Elizabeth Johnson, 11 pages.
    - Johnson, William, 1782–1783 (Box 27, Folder 843)
      Copies of his letters to various recipients, including Joshua Reynolds, John Palmer, Mr. and Miss Yonge, Dan Johnson, and his parents, William and Elizabeth Johnson. Includes notes on other correspondence.
    - Johnson, William, 1780 November 28 (Box 27, Folder 844)
      Fragment of a manuscript copy of a letter to his mother, Elizabeth Johnson, from Off Ghyretty, 12 pages.
    - Johnson, William, 1782 February 14 (Box 27, Folder 845)
      Fragment of a manuscript copy of a letter to his mother, Elizabeth Johnson, from Calcutta, 36 pages.
    - Johnson, William, 1782 May 7 (Box 27, Folder 846)
      Fragment of a manuscript copy of a letter to his mother, Elizabeth Johnson, 5 pages.
    - Johnson, William, 1785 July 17 (Box 27, Folder 847)
      Autograph letter, signed, to his sister, Elizabeth Johnson, from Calcutta, 27 pages.
    - Johnson, William, 1776 September (Box 28, Folder 848)
      Fragment of a manuscript copy of a letter to Samuel Johnson, 22 pages.
    - Johnson, William, 1797 January 11 (Box 28, Folder 849)
      Autograph letter, signed, to William and Thomas Raikes, from Calcutta, 8 pages.
    - Johnson, William, 1782 December 3 (Box 28, Folder 850)
      Fragment of a manuscript copy of a letter to Sir Joshua Reynolds, 8 pages.
    - Johnson, William, 1797 November 6 (Box 28, Folder 851)
      Autograph letter, signed, to "Dear Johnson," 4 pages.
    - Johnson, William, 1795–1797 (Box 28, Folder 852-858)
      Seven letterbooks containing copies of legal documents and business correspondence.
    - Johnson, William, 1795–1797 (Box 28, Folder 859)
      Typed transcript of the seven letterbooks containing copies of legal documents and business correspondence.
    - Johnson, William, 1795–1797 (Box 29, Folder 860-861)
    - Johnson family, 1780–1874 (Box 29, Folder 862)
      Diary covering events of the Johnson family, primarily the period from 1780 to 1874, taken from the letters and journals of various family members. Includes a list of photographs, drawings, etc. on the first two pages and a list of clerical descendants and inter-marriages with Reynolds on page 48. Written in ink, pencil, and blue pencil in several hands. 51 pages. Includes the following laid in:
      1. Martin, J. Portion of a letter to Miss Johnson, 1824 July 19.
      2. Notes, 2 leaves.
      3. Clipping on aurora borealis, 1831 January 7, with a manuscript note on the verso.
      4. Peurore, John. Letter to Miss Johnson.
      5. Diary, covering 1768-1800, 12 pages.
      6. Letter dated 1818 September 5, 3 pages. 7. Clipping, "Coaching Extraordinary...", January 1873.
      8. J., E. M. Letter to Mr. Sutton, 2 pages.
      9. Obituary clipping about Lord Harris.
      10. Obituary clipping about Lord Rolly.
    - Lemairre, S. C., 1773? September 20; 1773 September 20 (Box 29, Folder 863)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Mr. Johnson, 3 pages.
    - Morgan, William?, 1832 November 27 (Box 29, Folder 864)
      Manuscript relating to an advowson titled "Queries for Mr. Morgan." Signed by "Will Morgan, Equitable Assurance Office."
    - Prescott, Latitia Elizabeth (Tolley), 1798? (Box 29, Folder 865)
      Four autograph letters, signed, to Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley) Johnson.
    - Scott, Thomas, 1810 October 25 (Box 29, Folder 866)
    - Sercar, Jaggornaut, 1784 December 8 (Box 29, Folder 867)
      Letter in the hand of an amanuensis to Anna Maria Tolley, from Calcutta, 4 pages.
    - Tolley, Anna Maria, 1781 May 15 (Box 29, Folder 868)
      Autograph letter, signed, to Lady Elizabeth Andrews, from Calcutta, 1 page.
    - Tolley, Anna Maria and William, 1788–1798 (Box 30, Folder 869)
      Letterbook containing copies of letters to Anna Maria Theresa (Tolley) Johnson and William Johnson, as listed below.
      Letter (copy) to Anna Maria Theresa Johnson, 2 pages. With letter to William Johnson on pages 3-4.
      Letter (copy) to Anna Maria Theresa Johnson, 4 pages.
      Letter (copy) to Anna Maria Theresa Johnson, London, 2 pages.
      Letter to Anna Maria Theresa Johnson, 4 pages. Begins "Your letter by the Rodney..."
      Letter to William Johnson, 2 pages.
      Letter to Anna Maria Theresa Johnson, 4 pages. Begins "I wrote to you about a fortnight ago..."
      Letter (copy) to Anna Maria Theresa Johnson, 3 pages.
      Letter to William Johnson, 3 pages. Begins "I have just finished a letter..."
      Letter to William Johnson, 2 pages, with address. Begins "I have not above five minutes..."
      Letter to Anna Maria Theresa Johnson, 2 pages. Begins "I have just heard that a shipages.."
      Letter to William Johnson, 3 pages.
      Letter to William Johnson, 2 pages. Begins "Oh My dear Johnson-How can I sufficiently..."
      Letter to Anna Maria Theresa Johnson, 2 pages. Begins "I have already written twice..."
      Letter to Anna Maria Theresa Johnson, 3 pages. Begins "I hope this letter will find you as well..."
      Letter to William Johnson, 4 pages. Begins "The Account you gave me..."
      Letter to Anna Maria Theresa Johnson, 1 page. Begins "Just as I was making..."
      Letter to Anna Maria Theresa Johnson, 1 page.
      Letter to Anna Maria Theresa Johnson.
      Letter to Anna Maria Theresa Johnson, 3 pages.
      Letter to William Johnson, 2 pages. Begins "My Nephew John Tottingham..."